=Revenge of Royal Princess=
= انتقام الأميرة الملكية =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
Han Shu
هان شو
stood me up again.
وقفني مرة أخرى.
Xie Yugui.
شيه يوجوي.
Would you like to hang out with me?
هل ترغب في التسكع معي؟
Well.
نحن سوف.
You look so much like my sister.
أنت تشبه كثيرا أختي.
It's too ostentatious for you to go out like this.
إنه لأمر تفاخر للغاية بالنسبة لك أن تخرج بهذه الطريقة.
Wouldn't it be more ostentatious
ألن يكون أكثر تفاخرًا
for Your Majesty to go out like this?
لجلالتك أن تخرج هكذا؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
(Zuixianju Tavern)
(حانة Zuixianju)
You look so beautiful.
تبدى جميلة جدا.
Save it.
احفظها.
Let's drink.
لنشرب.
In the past, Royal Princess and I
في الماضي ، أنا و Royal Princess
often ran out of the palace to drink like this.
غالبًا ما كان ينفد من القصر ليشرب مثل هذا.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Sister could hold her liquor.
الأخت يمكن أن تمسك الخمور لها.
To be honest,
لأكون صريحا،
I was afraid of the dark when I was a kid.
كنت خائفة من الظلام عندما كنت طفلاً.
Sister told me stories
أخبرتني الأخت القصص
and coaxed me to sleep.
وأقنعني بالنوم.
If I was being bullied,
إذا كنت أتعرض للتنمر ،
she would ask him to race a horse.
كانت تطلب منه أن يتسابق على حصان.
Guess what happened?
خمن ماذا جرى؟
What?
لما؟
She took the opportunity to kick the man off the horse.
انتهزت الفرصة لطرد الرجل من على الحصان.
And his limbs were all broken.
وكانت جميع أطرافه مكسورة.
You look so beautiful.
تبدى جميلة جدا.
Nice staff.
فريق عمل لطيف.
- You! - You are courting death.
- أنت!  - أنت تغازل الموت.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Please spare my life!
ارجوك احفظ حياتي!
Piss off!
اغرب عن وجهي!
How dare him covet my beauty?
كيف يجرؤ على اشتهاء جمالي؟
You'd better not lose
من الأفضل ألا تخسر
such an important thing.
مثل هذا الشيء المهم.
Li Xie.
لي شيه.
Sister.
أخت.
(Buddha)
(بوذا)
This is the peace buckle that I prayed for three months.
هذا هو مشبك السلام الذي صليت به لمدة ثلاثة أشهر.
Keep it well.
احتفظ بها بشكل جيد.
Look good?
تبدو جيدا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Sister, let's play together.
أختي ، لنلعب معًا.
(Buddha)
(بوذا)
Sister.
أخت.
I am Shu.
انا شو.
Sister, don't go.
أخت ، لا تذهب.
Sister.
أخت.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Are you having nightmares?
هل لديك كوابيس؟
Why are you not her?
لماذا لست هي؟
Say you love me.
قل أنك تحبني.
I love you.
أحبك.
King Regent.
الملك ريجنت.
Get out.
اخرج.
You are not allowed to come in
لا يسمح لك بالدخول
without my order.
بدون طلبي.
I tried on the makeup
جربت الماكياج
you made on me earlier.
قمت به علي في وقت سابق.
Look alike?
يبدو مشابها؟
Shu.
شو.
Don't speak to me
لا تتحدث معي
in her tone.
في لهجتها.
This round doesn't count.
هذه الجولة لا تحسب.
Once more.
مرة أخرى.
Your Majesty just stole my five chess pieces?
جلالة الملك سرق للتو قطع الشطرنج الخمس الخاصة بي؟
But even so,
ولكن على الرغم من ذلك،
you will definitely
سوف تفعل ذلك بالتأكيد
lose this round
تفقد هذه الجولة
within ten steps.
في غضون عشر خطوات.
Sister taught you so much,
علمتك الأخت كثيرا ،
but you haven't learned anything except cheating.
لكنك لم تتعلم أي شيء سوى الغش.
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
Once more.
مرة أخرى.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Come on.
تعال.
I don't know if I should tell you something or not.
لا أعرف ما إذا كان علي إخبارك بشيء أم لا.
Then don't.
ثم لا تفعل.
Today I passed by the back garden
اليوم مررت بالحديقة الخلفية
and accidentally ran into
واصطدمت بطريق الخطأ
sister Xie having fun
الأخت شيه يلهون
with someone there.
مع شخص ما هناك.
Her clothes are still hanging on the branch.
ما زالت ملابسها معلقة على الغصن.
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(تنتمي حصريًا إلى Tencent.)